<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nikunj Gupta</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nikunj Gupta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Echoes of Progress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/01-echoes-of-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/01-echoes-of-progress/</guid>
      <description>In the realm of technology, innovation is the beating heart that drives progress forward. From the humble beginnings of the first computers to the cutting-edge advancements in artificial intelligence and quantum computing, humanity&amp;rsquo;s quest for knowledge and efficiency knows no bounds. Each breakthrough builds upon the foundation laid by those who came before, propelling us ever closer to a future defined by boundless possibilities. Yet, with these remarkable achievements also come ethical considerations, as society grapples with questions of privacy, autonomy, and the ethical implications of our increasingly interconnected world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growth vs. Scale</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/02-growth-vs-scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/02-growth-vs-scale/</guid>
      <description>The concepts of growth and scale can be explored through the lens of personal development and societal progress. Growth, in this sense, refers to qualitative improvements and enhancements in characteristics, knowledge, wisdom, and personal capabilities. It is an inward journey that involves deep self-reflection, learning from experiences, and evolving through challenges. Growth is about becoming more complex and enriched in understanding, values, and virtues.
Scale, on the other hand, suggests a quantitative expansion, involving the ability to replicate or extend influence or impact effectively across larger ideas or to a broader audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I don&#39;t like the guy!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/04-i-dont-like-the-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/04-i-dont-like-the-guy/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t like the guy. Do I have reasons? Yeah. Good reasons? Yeah! How many reasons do I need? None. I don&amp;rsquo;t like the guy. It&amp;rsquo;s not about catching him in the act or exposing every lie he&amp;rsquo;s ever told. It&amp;rsquo;s deeper than that. It&amp;rsquo;s the way he speaks with a silver tongue, weaving tales that sound too good to be true. It&amp;rsquo;s the way his eyes shift when you ask him a straightforward question, the way his stories change with every retelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Time Value of Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/03-the-time-value-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/03-the-time-value-of-time/</guid>
      <description>The time value of money is a fundamental concept in finance that states that a dollar today is worth more than a dollar in the future. This is because money can earn interest or return when invested or saved. Building on this principle, the time value of &amp;ldquo;time&amp;rdquo; can underscore the importance of how we choose to spend our time, recognizing it as a precious and finite resource. Investing time thoughtfully can lead to personal growth, stronger relationships, and greater life satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unplanned Road Trip</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/05-the-unplanned-road-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scribbles/05-the-unplanned-road-trip/</guid>
      <description>So here’s the thing about unplanned road trips: they’re absolute chaos wrapped in pure magic. Seriously, you think you’re just going to get a coffee, and next thing you know, you’re three states over with a trunk full of questionable souvenirs and a story that will last a lifetime.
It started with a simple plan. Or rather, the lack of one. My friend Jake shows up at my door, eyes gleaming with that wild look that says, “Trust me, this will be epic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
